A Guide to the Population Council records, Public Information Office and Publications, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 14 FA1434
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Public Information Office and Publications, 1965-1980; 14
  - French Translation Project, 3
    - Post-1976 French Activities (Box 16, Folder 258)
    - Commericial Distribution of Population Council French Books (Box 16, Folder 259)
    - Sale of Publications - AID Approval - French Translations (Box 16, Folder 260)
    - Harcourt's Glossary of French-English Terms (Box 16, Folder 261)
    - French Mailing List, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 262)
    - French Mailing List, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 263)
    - French Project Book 1970-1971 - Projects 1-37 (1970), Projects 38-74 (1971) (Box 16, Folder 264)
    - French Project Book 1972 - Projects 75-106 (Box 16, Folder 265)
    - French Project Book 1973 - Projects 107-142 (Including Project 44) (Box 16, Folder 266)
    - French Project Book 1974 - Projects 143-165 (Box 17, Folder 267)
    - French Project Book 1975-1976 - Projects 166-179 (Box 17, Folder 268)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning 1970, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 268A)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 269)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning, Vol. 2, No. 1-12, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 270)
    - Population Council Special Publications (English), 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 271)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning, Vol. 3, No. 1-12, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning, Vol. 4, No. 1-12, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 273)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning, Vol. 5, No. 1-12, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 274)
    - French Language Publications - Studies in Family Planning, Vol. 6, No. 1-12, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 275)
    - French Language Publications, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 276)
    - French Language Publications - "Current Publications", 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 277)
    - French Language Publications - Country Profiles, 1970-1975 (Box 19, Folder 278)
    - French Language Publications - Bulletins, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 279-280)
    - French Language Publications - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 281)
    - French Language Publications - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 282)
    - English and French Language Publications - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 283-285)
    - English and French Language Publications - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 286)
  - Spanish Translations Project, 4
    - Population Council Newsletter (Internal), 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 287-288)
    - Spanish Translations - Procedures and Distibution (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - Spanish Translations Program 1975 - T75.10A (Box 21, Folder 290)
    - Regional Technical Aid Center, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - Editorial-Pax Mexico - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 292)
    - Spanish Subcommittee - Distributions and Rejections, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 293)
    - Spanish Translations - General Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 294)
    - Berg, The Nutrition Factor, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 295)
    - Fendall, Auxiliaries in Health Care, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - ACEP - Administration of Grant A74.1A, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - ACEP - Administration of Grant A74.1A, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 298)
    - A74.1A - Studies in Family Planning Projects, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - A74.1A - Country Profiles Projects, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 300)
    - A74.1A - Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 301)
    - S74-21 - Evaluation of Spanish Translation Program, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 302)
    - Presser - Sterilization and Fertility Decline in Puerto Rico, S74-16, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 303)
    - Arriaga - Mortality Decline and its Demographic Effects in Latin America, S74-15 (Box 23, Folder 304)
    - Hatcher - Contraceptive Technology, S-6, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 305)
    - Kocher - Rural Development, Income Distribution and Fertility Decline, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 306)
    - ACEP - Administration of Grant A73.3A, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 307)
    - Ministry of Health Manuals, S73-25, S74-17, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 308)
    - ACEP - A72.55A - Financial Reports, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 309)
    - KAP Manual - Spanish Edition, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 310)
    - Studies in Family Planning - Spanish Editions, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - Reports Files, 5
    - Reports - No. 1 - Contraceptive Technology, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 353)
    - Reports - No. 2 - Population and Family Planning Programs: A Fact Book, 1969-1976 (Box 28, Folder 354)
    - Reports - No. 3 - Macuro - Government Policy Statements on Population Control (Box 28, Folder 355)
    - Reports - No. 4 - Sollins - Commercial Production and Distribution of Contraceptives, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 356)
    - Reports - No. 5 - Presser - Voluntary Sterilization, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 357)
    - Reports - No. 6 - Robinson - Population Growth and Economic Welfare, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 358)
    - Reports - No. 7 - Schramm - Communication in Family Planning, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - Reports - No. 8 - Forrest - Postpartum Services in Family Planning, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - Reports - No. 9 - Wray - Population Pressures on Families, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 361)
    - Reports - No. 10- Jones - Mobile Units, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - Reports - No. 11 - Little - Commercial Distribution of Contraceptives in Colombia, Iran and the Philippines, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 363)
    - Reports - No. 12 - Findings from Family Planning Research in Latin America, Supplement, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 364)
    - Reports - No. 13 - Stamper - Population Policy in Development Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 365)
    - Reports - No. 14 - Tietze - Enduced Abortion: A Fact Book, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 366)
    - Reports - No. 15 - Berelson - World Population: Status Report 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 367)
    - Reports - No. 16 - Nortman - Parental Age as a Factor in Pregnancy Outcome, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 368)
    - Dixon - Women's Rights and Fertility, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 369)
    - Status Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 370)
    - Reports - Advisors, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - Reports - Review, 1973 Fall (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - Reports - Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 373)
    - Reports - Review Committee, 1975 October (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - Reports - Advisory Groups, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Reports - Reviews 1973 (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - Country Prospects - Complete Set, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 377)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Schedules, Mailings and Distribution Files (Box 30, Folder 378-383)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Background and Distribution Files (Box 31, Folder 384-415)
    - Alumni Information Series, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 416-418)
    - Studies - ICCR Computer Program - Distribution Policy, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 419)
    - Cairo Conference Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 420)
    - CBR Display - Original Materials for 1962 Intrauterine Contraceptives Conference (Box 32, Folder 421)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Notes and Drafts - Final Draft, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 422)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Notes and Drafts (Box 32, Folder 423-426)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Notes and Drafts (Box 33, Folder 427-430)
    - Population Council 25-Year History 1952-1977 Report - Notes and Drafts (Box 34, Folder 431-433)
    - Miscellaneous Historical Material (Box 34, Folder 434)
    - Evaluations of the Population Council, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 435-440)
  - Basic Library Program, 6
    - Book Lists and Supplements, 1967-1974 (Box 36, Folder 441)
    - Program Files - McInnes, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 442-444)
    - Geographic Distribution Report - McInnes, 1974-1976 (Box 37)
    - Stock Status Report - McInnes, 1975-1976 (Box 37)
  - Population Council Annual Reports, 1952-1972; 7
    - Population Council Annual Reports, 1952-1972 (Box 38, Folder 445-447)
  - Books and Occasional Papers Program, 8
    - Book Program - Status Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 448)
    - Type Specifications - Occasional Papers Series (Box 39, Folder 449)
    - Publications Committee, 1969-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 450)
    - Publications Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 39, Folder 451)
    - Elsevier Series Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 452)
    - McGraw-Hill - Contracts, 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 453)
    - McGraw-Hill Series - Rejects (Box 39, Folder 454)
    - McGraw-Hill - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 455)
    - McGraw-Hill - Contracts, 1969-1974 (Box 39, Folder 456)
    - U.S. Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Index Volume - Budget (Box 39, Folder 457)
    - U.S. Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Index Volume - Corespondence (Box 40, Folder 458)
    - Bean - Population and Family Planning: Manpower and Training - Reviews (Box 40, Folder 459)
    - Bean - Population and Family Planning: Manpower and Training (Box 40, Folder 460)
    - Berelson - The Great Debate (Box 40, Folder 461)
    - Berelson - Population Policy - Distribution (Box 40, Folder 462)
    - Berelson - Population Policy (Box 40, Folder 463)
    - Callahan - Ethics and Population (Box 40, Folder 464)
    - David - Family Planning and Abortion in Socialist Countries, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 465)
    - Caldwell - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 466)
    - Caldwell - Correspondence with Publishers, and Distribution, 1971-1975 (Box 40, Folder 467)
    - Duza and Baldwin - Nuptiality and Population Policy, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 468)
    - Fawcett - Psychological Aspects of Population Control (Box 40, Folder 469)
    - Fawcett - Psychological Aspects of Population Control - Reviews (Box 40, Folder 470)
    - Fawcett - Psychological Aspects of Population Control - Production (Box 41, Folder 471)
    - Freedman and Coombs - Comparative Fertility Research (Box 41, Folder 472)
    - Friedman - Production Estimates (Box 41, Folder 473)
    - Friedman - Memos and Author Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 474)
    - Friedman - Laissez Faire in Population - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 475)
    - Freedman - Sociology of Human Fertility (Box 41, Folder 476)
    - John Wiley and Sons - Wiley Interscience (Box 41, Folder 477)
    - Frejka - The Future of Population Growth - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 478)
    - Frejka-Wiley - Distribution (Box 41, Folder 479)
    - Henry - Negotiations with Publishers (Box 41, Folder 480)
    - Henry Book - Population Council Distribution, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 481)
    - Henry - Current Letters and Information (Box 41, Folder 482)
    - Jones - The Economic Effect of Declining Fertility - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 483)
    - KAP Manual - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 484)
    - Jones - The Economic Effect of Declining Fertility - Documentation, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 485)
    - Jones, Gavin - Population Growth and Educational Planning in Developing Nations - Publisher (Box 41, Folder 486)
    - Jones, Gavin - Population Growth and Educational Planning in Developing Nations - Author Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 487)
    - Kim et al. - Korean Family Planning Program - Distribution and Reviews (Box 41, Folder 488)
    - Kim, Rose, Worth - Production File (Box 41, Folder 489)
    - Kocher - Rural Development, Income Distribution and Fertility Decline (Box 41, Folder 490)
    - Kocher - Rural Development, Income Distribution and Fertility Decline - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 491)
    - Newman-Beck-Lewit - Abortion - Production File (Box 41, Folder 492)
    - Newman-Beck-Lewit - Abortion - Reviews (Box 41, Folder 493)
    - Nortman - Model Relations Between Birth Rates and Birth Control Practice, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 494-495)
    - Seltzer - PGE Handbook, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 496)
    - PGE Handbook - Reviews (Box 42, Folder 497)
    - PGE Handbook - Correspondence with Authors - Revisions (Box 42, Folder 498)
    - Seltzer - PGE Handbook - Distribution (Box 42, Folder 499)
    - Robinson - Population and Development Planning Volume - Distribution (Box 42, Folder 500)
    - Robinson - Production (Box 42, Folder 501)
    - Muslim Attitudes Revised Edition (Box 42, Folder 502)
    - Seltzer - Demo Data Collection - Reviews (Box 42, Folder 503)
    - Seltzer - Data Collection Techniques (Box 42, Folder 504)
    - Seltzer - Data Collection Techniques - Design and Distribution (Box 42, Folder 505)
    - Shorter - Population Projections (Box 42, Folder 506)
    - Simmons - Indian Investment in Family Planning - Reviews (Box 42, Folder 507)
    - Simmons - Indian Investment in Family Planning (Box 42, Folder 508)
    - Singer - Is There an Optimum Level of Population (Box 42, Folder 509)
    - Sivin Manuscript - Interoffice Memos (Pre-Completion) (Box 43, Folder 510)
    - Sivin - Reviews and Reviewers (Box 43, Folder 511)
    - Srikantan - The Family Planning Program in the Socioeconomic Context (Box 43, Folder 512)
    - Srikantan - Multivariate Analysis (Box 43, Folder 513)
    - Stamper - Population and Development (Box 43, Folder 514)
    - Stycos, J. Mayone - Ideaology, Faith and Family Planning in Latin America (Box 43, Folder 515)
    - Symonds and Carder - United Nations Agencies and Population Question (Box 43, Folder 516)
    - Taiwan Family Planning Reader, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 517)
    - FIGO - Post-Publication Activities (Box 43, Folder 518)
    - Watson - Family Planning in the Developing World, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 519)
    - World Review, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 520)
    - World Review - China, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 521)
    - World Review - East and Southeast Asia, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 522)
    - World Review - Latin America, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 523)
    - World Review - North Africa, Near East, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 524)
    - World Review - South Asia (Box 44, Folder 525)
    - World Review - Sub-Saharan Africa, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 526)
    - Zatuchni - Postpartum Family Planning, 1970-1974 (Box 44, Folder 527)